Italy has a manufacturing capacity
that is touching, and mind you,
this manufacturing capacity of the
people who truly make
the machines work like little artists, I
have only seen it in Italy.  There, you see?
Then in this room the drawings are born
and the drawings then become fabric,
textile.  This is where the
camouflage was born when William
became director
Vitton, artistic director.  This is the
winter version of the camouflage that
he will then present to the press at the
fashion show with.
This is nice.
Every week this wall changes.  These are
all the yarns that we make ourselves.
This is to do one of the things we
were asked to do, to say I want the
pointillist paintings, so all of
Sesra's paintings and then the pointillist, you see,
becomes this is a pointillist thread and
this instead is a pointillist thread with
more colors.  My real job is all
day we sit here scratching our heads
and trying to figure out what to do.  These are all the
tests that you will see in
the fashion shows in a couple of months.   You ca
n't say whose,
right?  And this is a
pointillist pure wool coat.